<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: iOS | Steven's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://stevenlordiam.github.io/blog/categories/ios/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://stevenlordiam.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-12T16:01:17-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://stevenlordiam.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Stevenlordiam]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[stevenlordiam@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New iOS App for Leetcode - Leet]]></title>
    <link href="http://stevenlordiam.github.io/blog/20150811/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-11T22:35:17-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://stevenlordiam.github.io/blog/new-ios-app-for-leetcode-leet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As I said in last blog, I have decided to develop a new iOS app for leetcode. I finished it in three days for the first version. After fixing some bugs and updated the UI for iPhone 6 and 6 Plus, I summited it to the App Store.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>You can see a demo as follow. Since it&rsquo;s the first version so it&rsquo;s pretty raw and needs further improvement. For instance, I haven&rsquo;t added the account login feature, and the UI needs more polish. I will solve these problems in the coming updates.</p>

<p> <img src="/images/blog_image/demo.gif"></p>

<p>I have hosted it on Github, maybe someday I will open source it.</p>

<p>Please download and try it yourself <a href="https://github.com/stevenlordiam/leet">here</a>. I appreciate any advice.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New iOS Side Menu Demo]]></title>
    <link href="http://stevenlordiam.github.io/blog/20150806/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-06T22:45:49-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://stevenlordiam.github.io/blog/a-new-ios-side-menu-demo</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently I was developing an iOS app for leetcode, I found when displaying the content menu, <a href="https://github.com/romaonthego/RESideMenu">RESideMenu</a> is good at showing the parallax effect for iOS 7/8 app. So I decided to deploy it on my app. But when I was adding more <code>UIViewController</code> to it, it had a bug. You can find the detailed issue I posted <a href="https://github.com/romaonthego/RESideMenu/issues/252">here</a>.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>After some source code reading, I found the solution: creating a subclass of <code>UIViewController</code> instead of <code>RESideMenu</code> as the README of RESideMenu said. Because the new <code>UIViewController</code> will behave as a separate <code>View</code> rather than the RESideMenu behavior. So you cannot connect them.</p>

<p>Beside fixing this bug, I also add more view to this project. You can see a demo below.</p>

<p> <img src="/images/blog_image/SideMenu.gif"></p>

<p>I have open sourced this project as a fork of <a href="https://github.com/romaonthego/RESideMenu">RESideMenu</a> and you can find the source code on <a href="https://github.com/stevenlordiam/SideMenu">SideMenu</a>.</p>

<p>Please make pull request or submit an issue if you have any advice.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
